[Music]
[Música]
Oh wait that one Wait wait Wait what
Oh espera esa Espera espera Espera que
were you guys shaking Princess is here
estabais meneando a Princesita está aquí
Javi from English gave me some
Javi el de inglés me ha mandado una
homework
tarea me
[Laughter]
[Risas]
help But why did he call me obese
ayuda Pero por qué me ha llamado obeso
But why did he call me obese let's see
Pero por qué me ha llamado obeso a ver
wait I'm going to answer him but no I don't
espera le voy a contestar pero no no
have the answer
tengo la respuesta
but I'm going to answer him
en pero es que le voy a contestar
princess I'm going to answer him princess
princesita le voy a contestar princesita
but really how annoying are they eh how
pero de verdad qué pesadas son eh qué
annoying are those two dude they don't leave me
pesadas son las dos tío no me dejan en
alone she chips at you she calls you obese you'll
paz te chipea te dice obeso le
remind her ok no I think I
recordarás sj no yo creo que le he
answered him in the best way possible the one
contestado de la mejor manera posible la
you have but let's see but let's see but let's
que te has pero a ver pero a ver pero a
see let's see what let's see what
ver a ver vamos a ver lo de vamos a ver
Abi did what happens is that of course to
lo de Abi lo que pasa es que claro para
see what Abi did I would have to put
ver lo de Abi yo tendría que poner un
the joke from the other day into context a little bit of
poco en contexto la funa del otro día
course Abi got angry I don't know
claro Abi se ha enfadado yo no sé por
why Let's see Abi got angry because they
qué A ver Abi se ha enfadado porque le
called her for one of the clips from the
han funado por uno de los clips de los
last few days okay What was the clip well
últimos días vale Cuál era el clip pues
this one Well yesterday okay a clip from yesterday  the
este Bueno ayer vale un clip de ayer la
han fun I didn't have it I didn't have that
han fun yo no tenía yo no tenía esa
intention the streamer Abi attacks
intención la streamer Abi arremete
all the creators who
contra todos los creadores que que
express right-wing ideals, that's
expresan ideales de derecha o sea
literally what she does Look this is
literalmente es lo que hace Mira esto es
a Take that I'm going to give because
un Take que pues voy a dar porque es que
today it really hits me today it hits me
hoy me sale los [__] hoy me sale los
clearly it's her who
[__] claro es que es ella es la que
got into this mess what's my fault it's
se ha metido este fregado yo qué culpa
obvious that in recent years there has
tengo es obvio que en los últimos años
been a trend that brings
ha habido una corriente que acerca a la
young people closer to the right To the
gente joven a la derecha A la familia
more
más
traditional family it's like we've regressed
tradicional como que hemos involucionado
a bit not how it feels like on social media we
un poco no como se siente así en redes
see a lot more sexist harassment you get
vemos mucho más acoso machista te metes
on Twitter and there are tons of accounts
en Twitter y Hay muchísimas cuentas
dedicated only to harassing insulting
destinadas solo a acosar a insultar a
women when you really think about it they
mujeres cuando te comes mucho la cabeza
can slip in this argument that you
te pueden colar este argumento de es que
've gone too far asking for things saying
se habéis pasado pidiendo cosas diciendo
that it's all sexual harassment eh making the
que todo es acoso sexual eh poniendo al
man look like the bad guy you've gone too far
hombre como el malo os habéis pasado
So we've had enough and we're going to be
Entonces nos hemos hartado y vamos a ser
[ __ ] baboons I don't give a
unos [__] mandriles a mí me suda la
damn I don't give a damn this argument I don't care if it
[__] me suda la [__] este argumento me
affected you that there are
da igual que te haya afectado que haya
some [ __ ] who can say it
algunas [__] que pueda decirlo de
machete well this nonsense machete
machete pues la tontería esta machete
macho or death to men I don't care what
machote o muerte a los hombres me da
you have Salted of that point
igual que te ha Salado de eso punto
number that does not represent me and
número eso no me no me representa y
point number two if you think that this
punto número dos si crees que esas
[ __ ] is reason enough
gilipolleces ya son razón suficiente
for you to stop fighting for
como para que entonces dejes de luchar
these things to stop happening or
porque estas cosas dejen de pasar o
simply turn around and continue
simplemente te des media vuelta y sigas
with your life as if this were not the
con tu vida como si esta no fuese la
reality you have always been, well
realidad lo lleves siendo siempre pues
what do you want me to tell you you are simply
qué quieres que te diga simplemente eres
a [ __ ] sexist person who
una persona jodidamente machista que
needed a minimal excuse to be able to
necesitaba una mínima excusa para poder
be openly without being judged
serlo abiertamente sin que la juzguen la
people have realized that they really
gente se ha dado cuenta que realmente
could always say what they wanted they have
siempre pudo decir lo que lo que querían
realized that being canceled is
se han dado cuenta que que te cancelen
useless and they have lost their
no sirve de nada y ya han perdido la
shame but and I also see it and I
vergüenza pero y también lo veo y esto
say this openly to my fellow
lo digo abiertamente a mis colegas
streamers I feel that lately there is no
streamers siento que últimamente no hay
one at the wheel, I mean people that I
nadie al volante o sea gente que me cae
genuinely like saying nonsense
genuinamente bien diciendo barbaridades
Stream because they are angry over a video game
Stream porque se pican por un videojuego
but I am not referring to nonsense like bua kill
pero no me refiero a barbaridades de bua
yourself bua [ __ ] who could be
mátate bua gilipo a quién se estará
referring to here bu no no nonsense eh
refiriendo aquí bu no no barbaridades eh
Well  everything that ends in fob Like
Pues todo lo que acabe en fob Como dijo
Borja escolana said once comma semicolon
Borja escolana una vez coma punto y coma
if you're going to say something stupid at least
si vas a decir una gilipollez al menos
say it with some cleavage now now for
dilo con un escote ahora ahora por lo
whatever Abi is watching this Stream and and
que sea Abi está viendo este Stream y y
and look at your super chat and she'll tell me that I
y mira tu super chat y me dirá que yo
allow a super sexist chat I don't think I do
permito un super chat machista No creo
n't think you chose the
que no creo que hayas escogido el
appropriate moment to give me those five
momento apropiado para darme esos cinco
bucks bico I mean people have lost their
pavos bico me refiero la gente ha perdó
fear and we are devolving
el miedo y estamos involucionando
impressive is that the most bought
impresionante es que lo más compró
Twitter the most what a son of a [ __ ] I
Twitter el lo más que hijo de [__]
also tell you I have also seen
también te digo también he visto a
streamers there is a t that I like a lot
streamers hay hay un t que me cae muy
but clo already liked yes Abi
bien pero clo ya le gustaba si Abi
Tell me year rejón totally
Cuéntamelo año rejón totalmente
totally very good that yorio very well very
totalmente muy buena esa yorio muy bien
well brought very well tra torra already
muy bien traído muy bien tra torra ya
with them clearer she liked the
con elos más claro aella le gustaba el
leftist Twitter that censored you
Twitter de izquierda que te censuraba
that you couldn't you know it puts many tweets
que no podía sabes lo pone muchos tweets
the Twitter that was red so unknown
el Twitter que era rojo así de descocido
with women many eh And I like it
con las mujeres muchos eh Y me cae
superb but I don't remember that there was a
superb pero no me acuerdo que hubo un
day that she put made the comment this the
día que puso hizo el comentario este el
worst enemy of a woman is another woman
peor enemigo de una mujer es otra mujer
me  I swear to God that every time I
yo te lo juro por Dios que cada vez que
read that phrase or hear it my
Leo frase o la escucho me hierve la
blood boils since the
sangre desde que está ocultado los me
Twitter likes have been hidden eh posts super incels
gustas de Twitter eh posts super incels
super sexist super racist super with
super machistas super racistas super con
tens of thousands of likes of course now
decenas de milas de likes claro ahora
since the likes have been hidden
desde que se han ocultado los likes la
people are no longer shy about liking the
gente ya no se corta en darle like a los
t Look at me with the gossip tweets there are
t Mira a mí a los twits de salseo hay
each one that I that starts liking
cada uno que yo que se pone a darle like
the tweets I no no no I tell you no
a los tweets yo no no no os lo digo no
but what I say everyone must gossip
pero que digo todo el mundo debe salseo
everyone everyone Of course because there I do
todo todo el mundo Claro porque ahí sí
see who sees it no and there are some
veo quien lo ve no y hay algunos que
but this guy sees the gossip or maybe
pero este tío ve el salseo o o a lo
people that I've messed with eh and he doesn't care
mejor gente con la que me he metido eh y
and and he likes it maybe ret
se la pela y y le da like a lo mejor ret
well challenge no that gives like to a post
bueno retar no eso le da like a a post
of gossip about things tens of thousands
de de salseo de cosas decenas de miles
of likes not only are you scum but
de likes no solo sois Escoria sino que
on top of that you are scared scoundrels
encima sois unos sinvergüenzas miedicas
you are scared scoundrels because
sois unos sinvergüenzas miedicas porque
when people could see it  what were you doing you did
cuando la gente podía ver lo que hacías
n't give those likes that's part of
no dabas esos likes eso forma parte de
the no coward [ __ ] before you didn't do it
la no cobarde de [__] antes no lo
and now that the likes are
hacías y ahora que los likes están
private you bring out your worst version of [ __ ]
privados sacas Tu peor versión de [__]
not only are you disgusting but you're a [ __ ] [ __ ] the
no solo das asco sino que eres un [__]
Blue Sky thing That's ridiculous
lo del Blue Sky Ese es una ridiculez
but that's the right to throw a tantrum
pero eso es el derecho a pataleta
basically okay I mean the thing about the people who
básicamente vale o sea lo de la gente
say well I'm going to sky blue to sky
que dice pues me voy a sky blue a sky
blue nobody is going to use sky blue nobody I
blue nadie va a utilizar sky blue nadie
mean it's not going to be a social network like
o sea no va a ser una red social como
Twitter of Popular of I don't know what of I don't know
Twitter de Popular de no sé qué de no sé
how much no no social networks Twitter
cuánto no no las redes sociales Twitter
okay that's a tantrum like Oh Oh Oh Ay I do
vale eso es una pataleta como Ay Ay Ay
n't want the most I want
Ay no quiero los más quiero que sea
Twitter to be progressive I want it not to be possible to
progre el Twitter quiero que no se pueda
say the word eh black do you remember I couldn't say the word black I couldn't
decir la palabra eh negro os acordáis no
say the word black I couldn't say you
decir la palabra negro no podía decir
know everything was racist everything was
sabes todo era racista todo era
ableist everything and they suspended your [ __ ]
capacitista todo y te suspendían la [__]
account at all times let's see one
cuenta a cada momento vamos a ver una
thing is one thing and another thing not one
cosa es una cosa y otra cosa ni un
extreme in the other something normal no Total
extremo en el otro algo normal no Total
that they've denounced her for this well let's see they've
que la han funado por esto bueno a ver
denounced her they haven't criticized her much
la han funado no la han criticado mucho
I don't know who  damn, he must have shared it, it
Yo no sé quién [__] lo habrá compartido
has a million views. This is worth it.
tiene un millón de visitas Esto vale
But hey, they've really joked about it, he got
Pero bueno la han funado mucho se ha
pissed off and dedicated a few
[__] y me ha dedicado unas
words to me live. Hey, finish watching the
palabritas en directo termina de ver el
cim, he tells me luare. Why are you scared?
cim me dice luare Por qué eh miedica
You're a coward, man. Twitter has
Eres un cobarde tío Twitter es se ha
become the worst social network. I feel like
convertido en la peor red social siento
people with influence and
que cada vez la gente con influencia y
power are going to talk about it less and less because they
poder va a hablar menos de ello porque
feel that if they talk about it, there will be a lot of
siente que si habla de ello habrá mucha
people against them and they will classify them as
gente en su contra y le catalogar de
something they don't want to be classified as to
algo que no quiere ser catalog ados por
be as populist as possible, to have as many
ser lo más populistas posible por tener
people as possible. I know that
a la máxima gente posible también Sé que
some networks also do it to
algunos de redes también lo hacen por
please the trend. There are obviously
contentar la moda hay obviamente
quite a few content types that I
bastantes ces de contenido que yo
know and I get along with them, but they
conozco y me llevo con ellos pero que
throw out a lot of the "I'm sexist but Jiji"
tiran mucho la de soy machista pero Jiji
or "I'm racist but Jiji" because Twitter
o soy racista pero Jiji porque Twitter
football fills you with mentions like that and gives you
fúbol te llena las menciones así y te da
all the validation you want,
toda la validación que tú quieras
so they look for the easy target. I
entonces buscan el target fácil yo te lo
swear I hear some [ __ ]
juro vuelvo a escuchar algún [__]
streamer again saying the ones with blue hair, the ones with the
streamer diciendo las del pelo azul las
blue hair, the ones with the
del pelo azul los de la bandera de
Palestinian flag, the ones with the
Palestina los de la bandera de de de los
gay flag, bro, brother, did you say it?  have you ever talked about it sometime
gays bro hermano has dicho alguna vez
about them taking
algo sobre que nos hagan a nosotras
pictures of us cona and undressing us or making fake
fotos cona y nos desnuden o hagan fake
voice notes with our voice so that
notas de voz con nuestra voz para que la
people get off have you talked about it well I haven't
peña se corra has hablado pues yo no he
seen that that S that have you ever
visto eso eso S eso alguna vez de ello
talked about it also about the
has hablado también de alguna vez de los
cases where it is proven that this
casos donde se demuestra que ese
streamer or this youtuber really
streamer o ese youtuber realmente le
wrote to minors or that he also assaulted
escribía a menores o que también agredió
x people and it has been proven have you
a x personas y se ha demostrado has
ever talked about these people why do
hablado alguna vez de esa gente por qué
n't you stop talking how how how how how how
no dejas de hablar cómo cómo cómo cómo
Abi once about it you have
cómo cómo Abi una vez de ello has
also talked about the
hablado también de alguna vez de los
cases where it is proven that this
casos donde se demuestra que ese
streamer or this youtuber really
streamer o ese youtu realmente le
wrote to minors or that he also
escribí a menores o que también eh
assaulted x people and it has been proven have you
agredió a x personas y se ha demostrado
ever talked about these people what
has hablado alguna vez de esa gente qué
nerve you have Javi I don't even know how many
morro tiene Javi yo no sé ni Cuántas
times I've seen you interact with
veces te he visto a ti interactuar con
youtubers who have interacted with
youtubers que han interactuado con
minors who have uh who have been
menores que han eh que que han sido
accused of abuse, I mean the other day I
acusados de abusos o sea el otro día te
saw you tweeting with one and I also
he vi tuiteando con uno y además se lo
put it to him Look [ __ ] Look at this This look Abi
puse Mira [__] Mira este Este mira Abi
last year a clip of the
el año pasado se viralizó un clip de la
streamer Abi in which she stated that she
streamer Abi en el que afirmaba que
would always believe any
siempre iba a creer a cualqu cuier
possible liar that a possible
posible mentirosa que a un posible
abuser, I am not going to harass anyone
abusador no voy a ir a acosar a nadie
when a victim comes out but I will
cuando una víctima sale pero la voy a
always believe her at first if it is if it
creer siempre de primeras si es si luego
comes out later that she is a liar I am going to
sale que es una mentirosa la voy a
recriminate her like the most worth it but
recriminar eso como la que más vale pero
cape for example that he was accused of
capa por ejemplo que fue acusado de
having sexually assaulted his girlfriend in
haber agredido sexualmente a su novia en
2022 they are going to let's just passed
el 2022 van a vamos a acaban de pasar
Look on the 28th 2 years have just passed 2
Mira el día 28 acaban de pasar 2 años 2
years cape we do not know of any complaint
años capa no conocemos ninguna denuncia
against the girl or that he said this No it is not being
a la chica ni de que esto él dijo No no
fixed in court How is it going
se está arreglando en el juzgado Cómo va
okay But whatever here you are
vale Pero bueno lo que sea aquí estás
stupid flirting like with my friends
tonte coqueteando en plan a mis amigos
no no I do not mean a flirting of a
no no me refiero a un coqueteo de de
flirting of a flirting eh You do not believe the
ligo de ligoteo eh No la crees a la
girl you believe him what does it depend on Abi of
chica lo crees a él de qué depende Abi
course what does it depend on the cave zuritos
claro de qué depende a la cueva zuritos
double standards they have to suck So
doble moral les toca mamar Entonces por
why don't you stop talking about the blue-haired ones
qué no dejas de hablar de las de pelo
and the feminists and those who
azul y las feministas y las que te
cancel you and such Why never  you talk about the
cancelan y tal Por qué nunca hablas del
rest why don't you talk about the
resto por qué no hablas de de de los
real problems not the four
problemas reales no de los las cuatro
stupid things they can tell you on Twitter
tonterías que te pueden decir en Twitter
that stay there and that's it Why don't you
que se quedan ahí y punto Por qué no
talk about the real thing Why don't you talk
hablas de la coso real Por qué no hablas
about a real problem that affects
de de un problema real que afecta a la
half of your colleagues well of your
mitad de tus compañeras bueno de tus
colleagues who are women no no they have not become
compañeros que son las mujeres no no se
so accustomed to not being
hab acostumbrado tanto a que no nos
sexually harassed on social networks and
acosen sexualmente en redes y nos
insulted and degraded that nobody says
insulten y nos degraden que nadie dice
anything nobody says anything because it is what it is is what it
nada nadie dice nada porque es lo que
is but I think that just
hay es lo que hay pero yo creo que al
as you can say that there are
igual que se puede decir que hay hombres
incredible men eh There are men who deserve to
increíbles eh Hay hombres que merecen
be locked up there are men who deserve to be exposed there are men
estar encerrados hay hombres que merecen
who deserve
ser escrachados hay hombres que merecen
a warning there are men who
un toque de atención hay hombres que
deserve a movement against them
merecen que haya movimiento en su contra
and that's it the problem is that
y punto y punts el problema es que
when there are people from above who are
cuando hay gente de arriba que está
involved in these things Well the issue gets
metida en estas cosas Pues el tema se
complicated it is
complica es mucho más difícil hablar de
much more difficult to talk about these things when your best friend streamer buddy is involved in the matter what a big nerve girl I have seen him m I have seen him take a picture with youtube that they are involved in in  and that they have
youtub que están metidos en en y que han
done disgusting things to women I
hecho cosas asquerosas a las mujeres O
mean, what a cheek girl, I mean, what a
sea qué morro más grande tía o sea qué
cheek to go out and point at
morro tan grande de salir tú a señalar a
anyone, tell anyone what they have to
nadie a decirle a nadie lo que tiene que
do or what they have to point out or what they
hacer o lo que tiene que señalar o lo
have to Scratch You don't know what
que tiene que Scratch No sabéis qué
happened yesterday, yesterday an Illuminati alignment occurred
ocurrió ayer ayer ocurrió una alineación
just like it Hi yesterday
Illuminati tal y como lo Hi ayer se
the stars aligned incels it was a
alinearon los astros incels fue un día
terrible day that is obviously going to leave
estrepitoso que va a dejar obviamente
havoc for a few days because this is how it
estragos unos cuantos días porque esto
works you know that it always has to
funciona así ya sabéis que siempre tiene
be a bit of a snowball and then it
que ser un poco de snowball y luego
disappears as usual but basically they
desaparece as usual pero básicamente me
uploaded to Twitter and Instagram the
subieron a Twitter e Instagram las
accounts of Clon cpam I think it's called
cuentas de Clon cpam creo que se llama
the incel this guy Javi Oliveira and
la de incel este tal Javi oliveira y
Wall Street Wolverine the
Wall Street Wolverine el triángulo de
Bermuda Triangle Ah Wall Street Wolverine
las bermudas Ah Wall Street Wolverine
answered this is not a
contestó a esto no es una Charo en
potential Charo you know what happened yesterday, yesterday
potencia sabéis que ocurrió ayer ayer
an Illuminati alignment occurred just
ocurrió una alineación Illuminati tal y
like yesterday the stars aligned
como lo ayer se alinearon los astros
incels it was a terrible day that is going to
incels fue un día estrep tó que va a
leave what the [ __ ] is terrible there you
dejar qué [__] es estrep tó ahí lo
are putting it what the [ __ ] is that it is
estáis poniendo qué [__] es eso est
terrible  what the [ __ ] is that obviously
estrepitoso qué [__] es eso obviamente
wreaks havoc for a few days because this is how it
estragos unos cuantos días porque esto
works you know it always has to
funciona así ya sabéis que siempre tiene
be a bit of a snowball and then it
que ser un poco de snowball y luego
disappears as usual but basically they
desaparece as usual pero básicamente me
put me on Twitter and Instagram How it is
subieron a Twitter e Instagram Cómo es
thunderous how it is star no no wait
estrepitoso cómo es estre no no espera
star thunderous n he can take it
estre estrepitoso n se lo puede tomar
badly he can take it badly the
mal se lo puede tomar mal las cuentas de
Clone accounts cpam I think it's called the incel one
Clon cpam creo que se llama la de incel
this Javi Veira and Wall Street
este tal Javi veira y Wall Street
Wolverine the Bermuda triangle
Wolverine el triángulo de las bermudas
trigonometry the Skull Trio Yesterday was
trigonometría el Trío Calavera Ayer fue
day You know eh I'm talking for a while
día Ya sabéis eh estoy hablando un rato
about X topic and obviously if I talk about
de X tema y obviamente pues si hablo de
that topic it has to be out everywhere
ese tema tiene que salir por todos lados
I have to get out eh news Abi talks
tengo que salir eh news Abi habla
about happens happens guys It is what it is
de happens happens guys It is what it is
eh on top of that Wall Street Wolverine as I
eh encima Wall Street Wolverine como
mentioned on the right he couldn't just
mencioné a la derecha no podía solo
upload the clip where he talked about it but he
subir el clip donde hablaba de ello sino
also took advantage and uploaded the clip of
que también aprovechó Y subió el clip de
roro from How long ago TR months months ago he's been
roro de Hace cuánto ya TR meses meses ya
doing it from roro well he uploaded it
hacelo de roro bueno que lo subió
too
también
and And how they like they like what they
y Y cómo les gusta les gusta lo que les
like Hey and well one has to
gusta Oye y bueno una una tiene que
eat  the incels and continue with their lives for
comerse a los incels y sigue con su vida
a while the nice thing about the internet guys is
un rato lo bonito de internet chicos es
that you click this wonderful button
que tú le das a este maravilloso botón
it's magical eh I mean this is come on
es mágico eh o sea esto es vamos
impressive you click that button
impresionante le das a Ese botón
everything disappears they don't exist they were
desaparece todo no existen fueron
products of my imagination and the worst thing is that
productos de mi imaginación y lo pero es
the most that has done is that if you
que el lo más que ha hecho que si ahora
block someone now you're still going to come out
bloqueas a alguien aún así te va a salir
live life guys I just hope that
viva la vida chicos yo solo espero que
the networks love Let's see, it's not going to
la redes amar A ver no te va a salir te
show you the answer if they're answering
sale la respuesta si está respondiendo
something or yes or yes it
algo o si o si
comes out Or if you go into the profile No but
sale O si te metes en el perfil No pero
for you it doesn't show someone blocked
en para ti no te sale alguien bloqueado
no well it becomes mega super fashionable you do
no pues sea se ponga mega super de moda
n't see for you anyone blocked
no te salen para ti ni alguien bloqueado
or anyone silenced and we
ni ni alguien silenciado y nos vayamos
all go there I mean it's more I hope I know that on
todos allí o sea es más ojalá se que de
Twitter incel Twitter soccer
Twitter incel Twitter fúbol cuentas de
right-wing accounts like everyone on Twitter well in x
derechas tal todos en Twitter bueno en x
and y the rest of normal people we go
y y el resto de gente normal nos vayamos
to skyblue can you imagine incredible it's
a skyblue te imaginas increíbl es
Twitter but I don't know Go there to sky blue
Twitter pero que no se V ahí a sky blue
that nobody that that's not going to go viral it's not
que nadie que eso no va a ser viral no
going to be a social that I mean that's
va a ser una social que o sea eso es una
[ __ ] that that's the typical tantrum from
chorrada esa eso es la típica pataleta
time to time  as for good I don't like
de vez en cuando de bueno no me gusta
Twitter what it has done the most
Twitter lo que ha hecho los más cosas
beautiful things Of course because the people who are
lindas Claro porque la gente que se está
going there are for the same reason, I mean
yendo ahí es por la misma razón es decir
my first clear is that what we call it
mi primer claro es que cómo le llamamos
is not a tweet a literal copy of Twitter
no es tweet una copia de Twitter literal
a literal copy of Twitter and and they
una copia de Twitter literal y y se
think that here they go, I mean here you are not going to
creen que aquí van o sea aquí no vas a
promote your live Javi nor
promocionar tus directos Javi ni ni
any youtuber is going to promote here a
ningún youtuber va a promocionar aquí un
video is going to have 4000
vídeo va a tener el vídeo 4000 visitas
more views because the promotion here is that it doesn't make
más porque lo promocion aquí es que no
sense this is not even seen by Peter
tiene sentido esto no lo ve ni Peter
this is what you have created like saying look look at
esto os lo habéis creado como decir mira
what kind of people we are eh Twitter you are going to go
mira qué gente somos eh Twitter te vas a
bankrupt you are going to go bankrupt eh as it is still
arruinar te vas a arruinar eh como sigue
right-wing this what is this what the
siendo de derecha esto qué es esto qué
[ __ ] is my first butterfly I'm dying what
[__] es mi primera mariposa me muero qué
cucu and this What is my first butterfly
cucu y esto Qué es mi primera mariposa
marip post my first I am not going to post the
marip post mi primer no voy a poner el
first tweet [ __ ] a kiss Eric the
primer tweet coñete un beso Eric el
first tweet [ __ ] me too it's that I really
primer tweet coñete a mí también es que
like to tease her I have not put
me gusta mucho picarla no le he puesto
Abi condemns all the unfaithful whether they are
Abi condena a todos los infieles ya sean
men or women even though she
hombres o mujeres a pesar de que ella lo
would do it even though she would be for
haría a pesar de que ella lo sería por
10 million euros really the
10 millones de euros realmente la
person who has been unfaithful is the one who
persona que ha sido infiel es la que se
deserves to carry the negative conscience
merece cargar con la conciencia negativa
of what they have done and
de lo que ha hecho
if you don't get rid of it Hey, I have been
y eno te desprendes de eso Oye he sido
unfaithful to such and such a person you put them in
infiel tal a la otra persona la metes en
the mess of their life and you free yourself I don't know
el marrón de su vida y t te liberas no s
if you understand what I'm trying to
si me entendéis lo que estoy queriendo
say that they are much more insecure and that is
decir que sea mucho más insegura y por
precisely why we are
eso justo por
going to have an expert here
eso vamos a tener aquí a una experta
please lower your voice
baja la voz por favor
okay
vale
gita already pseudo all this is impressive I
gita ya seuda todo esto es impresionante
don't know who one is it was Wanger but the
no sé quién es uno era wanger pero el
other I don't know who he was at least being unfaithful,
otro no sé quién eraa menos ser infiel
woman or men, do you think it's a question
mujer o hombres cre que con es cuestión
of gender honestly I have seen some
de género sinceramente he visto a
very sons of [ __ ] women and I have seen some
mujeres muy hijas de [__] y he visto a
very filthy and unfaithful men, I mean
hombres muy guarros e infieles es decir
immature people who have zero respect for their
gente inmadura y que respeta cero a su
partner, they are everywhere it is not a question
pareja hay en todos lados no es cuestión
of gender it is a question of education, of
de género es cuestión sí de educación de
principles, of how your
principios de de cómo tengas amueblada
head is furnished and little else it is not about what you
la cabeza y poco más no se trata de que
have between your legs or what you
tengas entre las piernas o que te
feel What does my Fran say apart from saying
sientas Qué dice mi Fran aparte de decir
earned this girl has done something in her
ganadas esta chica ha hecho algo en su
life she dedicates herself  to stream and complains
vida se dedica a streamear y se queja de
that they talk about her crini should
que hablen de ella crini debería de
give her a talk but Fran You also
darle una charla pero Fran Tú también
have very I also had it and of and of
tienes muy Yo también la tenía y de y de
realized to cristinini eh I also
realizada a cristinini eh yo también la
had it but there were some little things you know
tenía pero hubo algunas cosillas sabes
But oh well nothing happens I
Pero bueno no pasa nada a mí me gusta
really like cristinini I mean I like her very much
mucho cristinini o sea me cae muy bien
very nice eh she's very pretty eh she's a hard
muy maja eh es muy guapa eh es muy
worker I mean I like how I like how she
trabajadora O sea me gusta como me gusta
does everything but yes it's true
como lo hace todo pero sí que es verdad
that we shouldn't deify anyone
que tampoco hay que endiosar a nadie
either eh eh I'm telling you eh for me all
tampoco eh eh te lo digo eh por mí todos
the unfaithful men and women burn in
los infieles y las infieles que ardan en
hell Eh I mean for me
el infierno Eh o sea para mí las
infidelities are the most
infidelidades son los de los actos más
disgusting acts creeping immature of
asquerosos rastreros inmaduros de
malice of a son of a [ __ ] I mean being unfaithful it
malicia de hijo de [__] o sea ser infiel
seems to me is a concept that doesn't
me parece es un concepto que a mí no me
fall my head I will never understand it I do
cae la cabeza jamás me va a caber no lo
n't
entiendo No lo
understand it and for 10 million and for 10
entiendo y por 10 millones y por 10
million Hey we have something left to see or I
millones Oye nos queda algo por ver o me
can go [ __ ] ourselves [ __ ] we have something left to
puedo illar cabrones nos queda algo por
see or what Hey but how has  little
ver o qué Oye pero cómo ha saltado
princess jumped to defend Abi
princesita para defender a a Abi
[Music]
[Música]
eh i
eh i